<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mfgarvin.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://mfgarvin.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-08-04T21:27:40-04:00</updated><id>https://mfgarvin.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Some Clever Webpage Name</title><subtitle>This site serves as a &quot;homebase&quot; of sorts for the various projects, thoughts, and varia that I&apos;d like to have on the World Wide Web. Probably won&apos;t be anything profound, but hey, who knows. Have a look.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hi! 👋</title><link href="https://mfgarvin.com/blog/2023/08/04/Hi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hi! 👋" /><published>2023-08-04T14:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-04T14:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://mfgarvin.com/blog/2023/08/04/Hi</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mfgarvin.com/blog/2023/08/04/Hi.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="humble-beginnings">Humble Beginnings</h1>

<p>So, Hello there! You’ve stumbled upon a blog, one upon millions of similar troves of text and thoughts out on the internet. I hope you enjoy your stay.</p>

<p>Just to give an idea of what this site is about - I built this site from scratch as a bit of a programming &amp; coding project over the summer of 2023. Yes, this includes the CSS, so if the styling seems somewhat elementary (or if it breaks, especially on mobile!), that’s why.</p>

<p>I’ve had this domain for a little while and I’ve gone through a couple different website hosting services &amp; content management systems, but all in all, I just want this site to be a little place to share a bit about who I am and to share a bit about the projects I’m working on. There could be some other various thoughts intermingled, though I wouldn’t count on it.</p>

<p>So yeah, that’s what I’ve got going here. Feel free to peruse, browse my code on <a href="https://github.com/mfgarvin">Github</a>, or even say hi over on <a href="https://www.twitter.com/mfgarvin">Twitter</a> (or X, or whatever it’ll be called in the future…). Thanks for stopping by!</p>

<p>Pax Chrisi.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humble Beginnings]]></summary></entry></feed>